<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<toeic>
<item>
<answer>as</answer>
<content>Mr. Park wants advertisers to purchase banners on his popular food blog SoDelish, as placing various ads for them would earn him income.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>displays</answer>
<content>Instructions for trade show exhibitors state that companies with booth reservations may set up their displays a day in advance.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>simpler</answer>
<content>Jennro Inc. has released an innovative Sureshot 456D camera that is a much simpler version to use than earlier models.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>in the event that </answer>
<content>in the event that stock runs out during the sale, a customer will be issued a rain check for the item that has sold out.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>purely</answer>
<content>Economic circumstances often force many household heads to accept orverseas jobs purely for financial reasons. </content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>duplicated</answer>
<content>The high-end watchmaker Gere has initiated legal proceeding against Rightwear.com, a retailer marketing inexpensive timepieces that duplicated Gere's trademarked style.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>thereafter</answer>
<content>A summary of the presentations will be given at the end of the day, and shortly thereafter , dinner will be served. </content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>circulation</answer>
<content>Although the government has released new banknotes with added security features, coins that have been in circulation fordecades will remain in use.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>rigorously</answer>
<content>The memo reminds supervisors to rigorously implement the new office dress code beginning next month.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>should</answer>
<content>Urban Textiles will not refund the down payment to Ms. Smith should she cancel her order after the products have been shipped.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>will be postponed</answer>
<content>Since the concert hall renovations are still not finished, Kevin Ockham's upcoming concert will be postponed to next month.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>promptly</answer>
<content>The design team was instructed to proceed promptly to the conference room for a meeting regarding some last-minute requests made by the client. </content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>he</answer>
<content>Mr. Andrews worked as the manager of an accounting firm before being hired by Albertson Financial, so he was an attractive candidate for the position. </content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>when</answer>
<content>All members of the Baja basketball team are required to commit to a diet that is heavy in protein and carbohydrates when training for the national games. </content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>whether</answer>
<content>There is disagreement among BF Electric's board members about whether to relocate its headquarters by the end of the year. </content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>be perceived</answer>
<content>Having worked hard for the managerial position, Mr Reiss hopes to be perceived as well-qualified for the new job.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>influential</answer>
<content>The CEO considers the supervisors influential in motivating the staff to increase their productivity. </content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>Although</answer>
<content>Although Mr. Baines traveled to the conference in New York by plane, he returned to Washington on an express train.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>applicable</answer>
<content>The winner of the monthly raffle, whose name will be announced on December 2, is responsible for paying all applicable taxes.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>impair</answer>
<content>Employees at Tenga Foods' warehouse are compensated by the company should injuries incurred on the job impair their ability to work.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>volatile</answer>
<content>According to economists, the price of agricultural commodities may be as volatile this year as they were a decade ago, whenprices spiked sharply before dropping.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>particulars</answer>
<content>Ms. Blake put together a tentative proposal for the client and agreed to work out the particulars of the contract in more detail next month.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>has merged</answer>
<content>Spec Glass has merged with Iron Spark and is now able to sell glass windows in both local and international markets.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>amounts</answer>
<content>The administration of the Vernon Medical Center is considering adjusting the amounts it charges for laboratory tests and outpatient treatments. </content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>through</answer>
<content>It takes only five minutes for vechicles to pass through the tunnel leading to the country's largest province. </content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>consult</answer>
<content>For exceptionally difficult cases, Mr. Hallis makes it a habit to consult his associates to make certain he takes the correct approach.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>accomplishment</answer>
<content>One major accomplishment of the local government has been to provide residents with efficient and adequate public transportation.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>combustible</answer>
<content>The petrochemical corporation follows strict requlations in regard to the transport of combustible chemicals, so as to protect staff from injury.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>diverse</answer>
<content>There are diverse sources of information online that can help those who are new to the stock market, but not all of these sites are dependable.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>courteously</answer>
<content>Attendants on the train treated all the passengers courteously and made sure they were comfortoeic during the trip.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>silence</answer>
<content>When his car alarm accidentally went off, Mr. Mitchell had to silence it right away to avoid disturbing his neighbors.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>particularly</answer>
<content>One of the highlights of the seminar was Mr. Choi's talk in how to deal with particularly difficult tasks.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>Because</answer>
<content>Because Dulce Country Club is already fully booked for May, suggestions for a suitoeic venue for the sports festival are needed.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>pursuing</answer>
<content>Students pursuing careers in journalism are advised to undertake their interships at publishing companies they would actually want to work at.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>repeated</answer>
<content>New advertisements are created periodically because repeated exposure to the same images can cause consumers to lose interest in a product.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>will be issuing</answer>
<content>A spokesperson for Simmons Firm said that the company will be issuing an official announcement about its expansion plans tomoritem afternoon. </content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>Disclosure</answer>
<content>Disclosure of private information on a social network is a risk that users face constantly because the internet is not one hundred persent secure. </content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>anticipated</answer>
<content>Due to some problems with the lease, Mr. Jackson has postponed his anticipated move to the new apartment by two weeks.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>progressively</answer>
<content>With the higer grade requirements for admission, it has become progressively more difficult for high school students to be accepted to Madison University. </content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>concentration</answer>
<content>Due to the region's low levels of rainfall, Arizona maintains the lowest concentration of plant and animal life in the country. </content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>which</answer>
<content>Numerous recreational activities are offered at Jade Panglao Resort, making it the perfect place in which to spend the holidays with family and friends. </content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>alternate</answer>
<content>Most outsourcing companies operate on alternate shift schedules to adequately accommodate their clients' needs.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>largest</answer>
<content>Merov Technologies, one of Russia's largest providers of telecommunication sevices, will launch more affordable boardband packages on June. </content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>cautiously</answer>
<content>The scientists are cautiously analyzing the results of their experiment to make sure the data in the concluding report is accurate.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>select</answer>
<content>Dream Day planning Company helps brides-to-be select the perfect dress, hairstyle, and makeup look for their special day. </content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>basically</answer>
<content>The couple basically knew they could not afford a place in the city, so they looked only in suburban areas.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>away</answer>
<content>Traffic officers are needed to direct drivers away from Cumberland Avenue as it is currently being repaved.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>attentive</answer>
<content>Bart's Bayou Bar and Grill is seeking an attentive waiter with a professional demeanor and extensive knowledge of Cajun cuisine.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>much</answer>
<content>The debut album of the montreal-based indie rock band Willow was released nationwide in February to much critical acclaim.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>initiative</answer>
<content>Employees should accept direction from their supervisor, but are also expected to take the initiative to solve any problems at work.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>referred</answer>
<content>After failing to provide a solution for Ms. Green's back pain, Dr. Lewis referred her to an orthopedic specialist at Grace Hospital.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>stabilization</answer>
<content>Signs of economic stabilization are evident, with higher employment rates and an increase in consumer spending.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>was put</answer>
<content>Kingston Construction Company was put under contract to erect a 15-story resort hotel by the end of the year.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>over</answer>
<content>After several months of negotiations, the dispute over working hours between management and the labor union remains in a deadlock.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>after</answer>
<content>Management promptly hired additional factory workers after orders for floor and bathroom tiles increased.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>ascribed</answer>
<content>The increase in volume of exports from Asia can be ascribed to innovative product design and assembly line technology.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>had</answer>
<content>Although Marla Ambers had difficulty adjusting at Gordem Entertainment Studios initially, she has since learned to cope with the fast-paced environment.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>improved</answer>
<content>According to the Department of Transportation, the additional street lights and road signs have led to improved safety conditions on the highway.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>conducive</answer>
<content>Classrooms are kept at a comfortoeic temperature to provide an environment that is conducive to learning.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>comparable</answer>
<content>Hermaine Electronics' newly-released photo printer is comparable in price and functionality to those of the company's market rivals.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>When</answer>
<content>When changing your mobile phone plan, please present valid identification at the customer service counter.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>was being designed</answer>
<content>An in-house training program was being designed for employees with leadership potential, but the manager decided to outsource the training instead.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>versatile</answer>
<content>The famous director found Rachel Burns to be sufficiently versatile to play almost any role, no matter how challenging.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>provisions</answer>
<content>All passenger vessels are required by law to make provisions for people with physical disabilities.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>Before</answer>
<content>Before Mr. Ware departs for Belgium next week, he will present his cost-cutting proposal to the logistics department at the company-wide meeting this Friday.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>According to</answer>
<content>According to TV-World's site policy, only those with paid memberships can stream television programs on their device.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>upon</answer>
<content>Whenever an important proposal has to be written, the manager always relies upon Mr. Watson, our long-time project writer.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>promoted</answer>
<content>Although promoted as low-fat fare, many ready-to-eat food items are actually high in sugar and other unhealthy ingredients.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>ambitious</answer>
<content>As soon as he assumed his new position, sales director Carl Reynolds set an ambitious target for the team for the next quarter.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>outgoing</answer>
<content>The Silvanus Museum staff is organizing a retirement party in honor of its outgoing director, who has served there for 25 years.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>approaching</answer>
<content>Spectators are purchasing tickets to the final match of the Wilbur Tennis Championship as the event is fast approaching .</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>transitions</answer>
<content>Most countries in Southeast Asia are undergoing gradual transitions from developing economies to industrialized nations.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>higher</answer>
<content>In relation to the other projects currently being implemented, the proposal writing task recently given by the supervisor is of higher importance.</content>
</item>
<item>
<answer>to bring</answer>
<content>Every six months, to bring its custormer database up-to-date, Filigre Insurance requests that clients provide current personal information.</content>
</item>
</toeic>